## Stefano Metafuni - Curriculum Vitae

Address 3 Lilybank Terrace, Dundee DD4 6BQ, Scotland, United Kingdom Date of Birth 6th August 1989 EU Driving Licence category A & B Nationality Dutch/Italian

Mobile Phone +44 (0)7902375570

E-mail metafunistefano@gmail.com

### **Personal Profile**

Astronomy graduate with focus on Physics, Mathematics and IT. Critical thinker with strong problem solving skills, keen eye for detail and well-developed analytical and numerical skills. Confident communicator, capable of working within a wide range of environments. Experienced in ecommerce with a strong interest in business development and technology. Commercially and customer focused, confident, flexible and communicative team-player with a drive to learn and continuously develop its own abilities.

### **Education & Certificates**

2015 <u>Minor in Education</u> - Second-degree teaching certificate in Physics - University of

Amsterdam (The Netherlands)

2008 – 2014 <u>BSc in Astronomy</u> – Leiden University (The Netherlands)

Dissertation project: installing, designing and implementing software in Python language for an All-Sky Camera, that is used to predict weather conditions and

determine best circumstances for astronomical observations. Developed to be used by

the Leiden Observatory.

2019 <u>Google Digital Marketing Certificate</u>

Google Analytics Beginner Certificate
Advanced Google Analytics Certificate

Udemy The Complete Digital Marketing Online Course Certificate

# **Technical Skills**

Web development languages:

 HTML5, CSS3/Sass, JavaScript (ES5 – ES6) and basic knowledge of jQuery and React Frameworks

Programming languages:

• Exposure to basic C++ and Python

**Business Intelligence Tools:** 

Knowledge and working experience of SAP, Oracle and CRM platforms Salesforce and Agile

## **Employment History**

June 2019 – Current

**Ecommerce assistant and Customer Service** | *Trade Counter Online – Dundee, UK*Responsible for the web-shop helpdesk, managing orders, online product-pages and selling on website and different selling platforms (Ebay, Amazon and Google Merchant Centre).
Revisiting, analyzing and optimising product pricing and product pages on base of online marketing and Search Engine Optimisation (SEO) principles.

Feb 2019 – May 2019

Technical Support | Dexcom - Edinburgh, UK

Technical support and advise for diabetes patients using the Dexcom products, in English language by e-mail and telephone. Resolving software related problems and identifying suitable products and solutions.

Oct 2017 – Feb 2019

**Technical Support/Senior Customer Service Agent** | *Harman Audio - Edinburgh, UK* Customer and Technical support for Harman Audio products in Dutch and English language. Communication with distributors, clients, customers and dealers by e-mail, telephone and chat on a daily basis. Online support as a subject matter expert and trainer for junior customer service agents. Development of training material, improvement of call center processes and translations.

Apr 2016 – Aug 2017

**Rental Sales Agent** | Avis Budget Group - Edinburgh Airport, UK and Schiphol Amsterdam Airport, The Netherlands

Exceeding required sales and upselling targets for the car rental company. Strong customer service skills in a fast-paced and international environment, striving to go the extra mile for the customers. Creating rental contracts for pre-booked reservations and walk-up business and leisure customers. Strict planning and organizing in limited timeframes, including planning of rental pick up appointments for Avis Preferred members, managing car park and fleet inventory. Leading the team and providing instructions and daily plans.

Sep 2015 – Mar 2016

**Education Officer/Advisor** | *Qompas - Leiden, The Netherlands* 

Customer service, supporting and advising tutors, mentors and deans of secondary schools. First point of contact for secondary schools for advice, back-up support and administrative service using an online learning platform. Didactical and learning advising using my educational background for secondary schools. Contributing to creating and writing online educative content for a large audience.

Feb 2015 – Aug 2015

**Physics/Science Teacher - Internship** | *Katholieke Scholengemeenschap (KSH) - Hoofddorp, The Netherlands* 

Second-degree Physics and Science teacher for several groups and levels on the secondary school KSH. Planning and starting new creative interactive lessons and developing own study material and exams. Effective class management with authority. Actively giving and receiving feedback to improve working style and teaching methods

Apr 2009 – Jul 2013

**Physics/Science and Mathermatics** Tutor | *Visser 't Hooft Lyceum and Bonaventura College - Leiden, The Netherlands* 

Private and groups tutor for Physics, Science and Mathematics subjects on secondary schools for all levels and years. Assisting in final exam training in Physics and Mathematics. Working with children with attentional disorders and autism, being a tutor and backup for students with extra needs

#### **Interests**

Web development and Marketing, Music, Travelling, Sports, International Culture and Cuisine